A Guide to the Robert W. Stewart Papers, 1970s-1990s
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Slides, Negatives, and Photographs
  - Negative 12, Interplan Office, 108 N. 1st Street (Box 8)
  - Negative 13, Interplan Office, 108 N. 1st St. (Box 8)
  - Negative 13-A, Masonic Temple, Broad Street (Box 8)
  - Negative 14, E.B. Sydnor, 6000 St. Andrew's Lane (Box 8)
  - Negative 15 (Job 7848), Stratford Hall (Box 8)
  - Negative 16 (Job 8010), V.C.U. Meeting Center (Box 8)
  - Negative 17, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous Richmond Houses (Box 8)
  - Negative 19, Gumenick Athletic Wing (Box 8)
  - Negative 20, Riverfront Project/Study (Box 8)
  - Negative 21, Central Belting Co. (Box 8)
  - Negative 23 (Job 8001), Barret House/Carriage House (Box 8)
  - Negative 24, (Job 8327), Talman Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 24-A, Emergency Shelter, Main St. (Box 8)
  - Negative 26 (Job 8022), Ben Dover Farm, Preston (Box 8)
  - Negative 27, V.I.P. 1975? (Box 8)
  - Negative 28 (Job 7305), Science Museum of Virginia (Box 8)
  - Negative 29 (Jobs 7808/7819), Hibbs Building (Box 8)
  - Negative 30 (Job 8018), Pace-King House (Box 8)
  - Negative 31 (Job 7837), Sonny Jones Residence Model (Box 8)
  - Negative 32 (Jobs 8558/8613), Christian Residence and Congregation Ami (Box 8)
  - Negative 33 (Job 8801), East Coast Oil #38 (Box 8)
  - Negative 33-A, Charles Department Store (Box 8)
  - Negative 34 (Job 8804), Unknown Sites (Box 8)
  - Negative 35, Various Found Negatives (Box 8)
  - Negative 36, Various Found Negatives (Box 8)
  - Negative 37, Various Found Negatives (Box 8)
  - Negative 38, Various Found Negatives (Box 8)
  - Negative 39, Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 8)
  - Negative 39-A, Orthal Residence?/Thalhimer Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 40, Turner Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 41 (Job 8736), Thalhimer Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 41-A (Job 8816), Thalhimer Residence #2 1988 (Box 8)
  - Negative 42, Unknown Interior Views (Box 8)
  - Negative 43, Downtown Richmond/Stratford Hall? (Box 8)
  - Negative 107 (Job 8531), 312 N. 25th Street (Box 8)
  - Negative 108 (Job 1208), Holt-Massey Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 109, Vera's Office Party (Box 8)
  - Negative 110, Clay/Marshall near 6th St. (Box 8)
  - Negative 111, Unidentified Houses/Structures (Box 8)
  - Negative 112, Arby's (Box 8)
  - Negative 112-A, Arby's/Pecher Beach House (Box 8)
  - Negative 113, Science Trailer/Science (Box 8)
  - Negative 114, Candlelight Committee (Box 8)
  - Negative 115, Robert Stewart House (Box 8)
  - Negative 116 (Job 8804) (Box 8)
  - Negative 117, Dryvit Installation Office (Box 8)
  - Negative 118, 203 N. Allen? (Box 8)
  - Negative 119, West End School #1 (Box 8)
  - Negative 119-A, West End School #2 (Box 8)
  - Negative 120, Village View (Box 8)
  - Negative 121 (Job 8635), Burrows Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 122, Unknown Church Interior (Box 8)
  - Negative 123 (Job 7910), Unknown House Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 124, 5th Street Team Model (Box 8)
  - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Film Canisters, Interplan Office, 108 N. First Street (Box 10)
  - Film Canisters, Interplan Office, 108 N. First Street (Box 10)
  - Film Canisters, Specs and Plans, 8613 or AMI (Box 10)
- Architectural Drawings
  The architectural drawings generated by Stewarts practice are located in map case drawers #40-67. The oversize planes are located above these map case drawers.
  - Accomack Co. Health Center (Oversize 40)
  - Adams T.T. Residence (Oversize 40)
  - Allau, Topper, Gloucester Co. 1991 (Oversize 40)
  - Allen, Matthews F., 3840 Margate Dr. (Oversize 40)
  - Allen, Thomas, 337 Clovely Rd (Oversize 40)
  - Amrhein Residence, 2117 Hanover Ave. (Oversize 40)
  - Arby's Ohio (Oversize 40)
  - Arby's International, Youngstown Ohio and Stone Rose Ave, Rocky (Oversize 40)
  - Arby's South East Corner 22nd Avenue and Main Street, Longmont Avenue, Colorado (Oversize 40)
  - Arby's Tidewater 1978 (Oversize 40)
  - Arby's Tidewater 1978 (Oversize 40)
  - Asian Scroll, n.d. (Oversize 40)
  - Asch, Andrew J. Jr. Residence, 7009 Riverside Drive (Oversize 40)
  - Asch, Andrew J., 7009 Riverside Dr. (Oversize 40)
  - Auditorium Expansion Schematic Study, Emporia, Virginia (Box 40)
  - Baer and Neblett, 2907 Hungary Springs Rd. [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Bainbridge Housing Complex (Oversize 41)
  - Bainbridge Housing Complex 1984 (Oversize 41)
  - Barker Residence, Goochland Co. [drawer 63] 1992 (Oversize 41)
  - Barnes, Frances and Lawrence Residence, 4703 Calumet Road (Oversize 41)
  - Barnfield, Ukrop's Shopping Center[drawer 63] 1995 (Oversize 41)
  - Barrett House, 13 South 5th Street [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Basement Office Plans, Libbie Avenue (Oversize 41)
  - Baskerville, George T. III, 104 Tuckahoe Blvd. 1985 (Oversize 41)
  - Bayless, Temple, Garden Plan (Oversize 41)
  - Baylor, Bessie, Hanover County, Va (Oversize 41)
  - Beaverdam Depot, Beaverdam, Va (Oversize 41)
  - Bellet, Mr. and Mrs. Leonard [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Belle Residence, 2521 Kensington Ave. [drawer 63] 1975 (Oversize 41)
  - Bell Telephone Building, Reston, Va (Oversize 41)
  - Bell, Ellyson Wilkins Offices [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Bellmont Sign [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Bellmont Topographical map (oversize) (Oversize 41)
  - Bendheim Residence, 10 Greenway Lane (Oversize 41)
  - Best Products Jewelry (Oversize 41)
  - Best Products Jewelry, Mall in Columbia, Md [drawer 63] 1984 (Oversize 41)
  - Beth Ahabah, 1109 and 1111 West Franklin St.[drawer 63] 1968 (Oversize 41)
  - Beth Ahabah Museum and Archives Plan (Oversize 41)
  - Blanton, Jack, Residence on Cary St. [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Blues Armory Theatre (Oversize 41)
  - Bnai, Birth, Proposed Plans (Oversize 41)
  - Boundry and Topographic Map, Block One, Hillcrest, Richmond (Oversize 41)
  - Bowles Residence, 11 Apmthill Rd. [drawer 63] 1991 (Oversize 41)
  - Branch Residence, 392 Clovelly Rd. 1991 (Oversize 41)
  - Brandon Episcopal Church, Prince George County [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Brandermill, Sunday Park, Chesterfield Co., [drawer 63] 1981 (Oversize 41)
  - Brent, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew, 31 Twin Lake Lane (Oversize 41)
  - Brent, Col. and Mrs. W.I.C., 823 Arlington Rd. [drawer 63] 1979 (Oversize 41)
  - Bristow Residence, 11 Bridgeway Road [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Brook Road, 5300 Block (Oversize 41)
  - Brooke Residence, 8103 University Drive (Oversize 41)
  - Brookfield, Mr. and Mrs. C.M., 8 Clarke Rd. [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Brookland Park Plaza, Brookland Park Boulevard and 2nd Avenue (Highland Park) (Oversize 41)
  - Bryan, Mr. and Mrs. John, 6300 Three Chopt Road (Oversize 41)
  - Bryan, Thomas P., Jr. Residence (Oversize 41)
  - Bryan, Thomas P., 6 Greenway Lane [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Burlingame, B.J. Residence, 2508 West Grace Street [drawer 63] (Oversize 41)
  - Burlingame, B.J. Residence, 2508 West Grace Street (Oversize 41)
  - Burrows Residence by landscape architect Charles F. Gillette (Oversize 41)
  - Butler Residence, Chase City Va, [drawer 63] 1975-1976 (Oversize 41)
  - C and P Telephone Company/Museum or Exhibition Space (Oversize 42)
  - Camp, Mr and Mrs. Paul D., Windsor Farms [drawer 64] 1949 (Oversize 42)
  - Camp, Mrs. Paul Residence, Landscape Designs [drawer 64] (Oversize 42)
  - Camp, Dr. and Mrs. Norman, 208 Overlook Rd. 1989 (Oversize 42)
  - Canal Walk Drawings [drawer 64] (Oversize 64)
  - Carreras Jewelers, Omni Hotel (Oversize 42)
  - Carrol's Drive In, 13801 Warwick Boulevard, Newport News (Oversize 42)
  - Carter, Dr. and Mrs. Hill, 303 College Avenue, Ashland 1991 (Oversize 42)
  - Carter, Dr. and Mrs. Hill, 303 College Avenue, Ashland, Virginia (Oversize 42)
  - Carter, Dr. and Mrs. Hill, 303 College Avenue, Ashland, Virginia 1963 (Oversize 42)
  - Carter, Troy Residence (Oversize 42)
  - Carter, Troy Residence (Oversize 42)
  - Casey's (for Southern Department Stores Inc.) (Oversize 42)
  - Casey's at Gloucester, Shouthern Department Stores (Oversize 42)
  - Casy's Inc (Department Store?), Colonial Williamsburg (Oversize 42)
  - Central Belting and Hose Rubber Co. (Oversize 42)
  - Channel 23 Site Map (Oversize 42)
  - Chapman, Rodney C. Residence (Oversize 42)
  - Chickahominy District, 49.85 acres (Oversize 42)
  - Christ Church, Reception Center (Irvington, Va) (Oversize 42)
  - Christ Church, Richmond (Oversize 42)
  - Christian, C. G. Residence, 6314 Three Road (Oversize 42)
  - Christian, Dixon Residence 101 Maple Ave. (Oversize 42)
  - 7603 Cornwell Road (did we move This...) (Oversize 42)
  - Cityscape Richmond (Oversize 42)
  - Clary, Mr. and Mrs. Amos Residence, Bolling Green, Virginia (Oversize 42)
  - Chadwick's Antiques (Oversize 42)
  - Chapman, F.W. Mrs., condominium 1982 (Oversize 42)
  - Cheek, Leslie Jr., Hollywood Cemetery (family plot) (Oversize 42)
  - Church Hill, 312 N. 25th Street (Oversize 42)
  - Christ Church, Lancaster, Va, Reception Center (Oversize 42)
  - Clement, Dr. and Mrs. Stephen Alterations and Additions to 5401 Cary Street (Oversize 42)
  - Combined Insurance Company of America, 1703 Parham Rd. (Oversize 42)
  - Commonwealth Professional Service Offices, 12 S. Auburn St. 1985 (Oversize 42)
  - Continental Enterprises, 616 East Franklin Street (Oversize 42)
  - Copenhaver Residence (Oversize 42)
  - Coppedge, Mr. and Mrs. W., 1807 Hanover Avenue (Oversize 42)
  - Corley Building, 214 E. Grace Street (Oversize 42)
  - Cox, James B., 7109 Pinetree Rd., 1980 [drawer 64] (Oversize 42)
  - Craddock Residence (Oversize 42)
  - Creeger, G., Residence, 419 Davis 1975 (Oversize 42)
  - Dabney, Todd, 1825 Park Ave. (Oversize 43)
  - Daffron, Phillip V., Magnolia Grange, Chesterfield Courthouse 1979 (Oversize 43)
  - Davenport, Claude (Oversize 43)
  - Dawnbarn Residence, 6426 Roselawn Road (Oversize 43)
  - Deane, Mr. and Mrs., Frederick, Jr. Residence [two sets] (Oversize 43)
  - Deane, Mr. and Mrs. H.C., Fr. Residence (Oversize 43)
  - Deaver, H.C. Matthews [County?], Va [two sets] (Oversize 43)
  - DeBoise, Residence, 4122 East Old Gun Road (Oversize 43)
  - Delano, Nancy and Hullihen Williams Moore (Oversize 43)
  - Deluxe Checking Printers (Oversize 43)
  - Dogwood Dell, Byrd Park (Oversize 43)
  - Dombalis Residence, 304 Sandalwood Dr. (Oversize 43)
  - Downtown Richmond Drawings (Oversize 43)
  - Dozier, C.L. Dabscreek, Lanscaster County, Va (Oversize 43)
  - Dujour Restaurant, 5806 Grove Avenue (Oversize 43)
  - Dunaway Residence, 2504 Kensington Ave (Oversize 43)
  - East Coast Oil Schematic Plans (Oversize 44)
  - East Coast Oil, New Car Wash 10150 Hull Street Road (Oversize 44)
  - East Coast Oil, 1420 E. Commerce Rd. 1985 (Oversize 44)
  - East Coast Oil Station 38, 2601 Mechanicville Turnpike 1988 (Oversize 44)
  - East Coast Oil Station #47; Exxon Co.; Humble Oil and Refining Co. 1967-1987 (Oversize 44)
  - East Coast Oil, 1420 Commerce Rd. (Oversize 44)
  - Easterly, Frank B. Residence, Bellona Arsenal, Chesterfield Co. (Oversize 44)
  - Edmunds Residence, 4714 Charmian Road (Oversize 44)
  - Ekstein's, Toilet Addition/Alterations to 6003 W. Broad Street (Oversize 44)
  - Ellyson Residence, 105 North Plum Street (Oversize 44)
  - Ellyson, William E. Residence, 4807 Pocahontas (Oversize 44)
  - Ellyson, William G., 1511 hanover Avenue 1972 (Oversize 44)
  - Elmington Gloucester, Virginia (Oversize 44)
  - Emporia, Downtown Revitalization Program; Pope's Family Center, Halifax (Oversize 44)
  - English, Dr. Bruce, 2214 E. Broad Street (Oversize 44)
  - Eskimo Pie Building, 530 East Main Street (Oversize 44)
  - Evans, Ronald S., 4211 Kingscrest Pkwy (Oversize 44)
  - Eveready Oil Company (Oversize 44)
  - Executive Office Building, Byrd Avenue 1902-1906 (Oversize 44)
  - Family Financial Center (Oversize 45)
  - Fan District, Richmond, Virginia Map (Oversize 45)
  - Farely Residence, Charles City Co. 1988 (Oversize 45)
  - Fekety Residence, 1806 Hanover Avenue (Oversize 45)
  - First and Merchants Headquarters, Alternative Proposal (Oversize 45)
  - First Merchant's Bank, V.C.U. Branch (Oversize 45)
  - Fitzgerald Residence, 16 Rio Vista Lane 1988 (Oversize 45)
  - Flohr, Mr. and Mrs. Wilson, Jr. at Windsor on the James 1989 (Oversize 45)
  - Fox Residence, 9400 Dpmpra Drove. Jemrocp (Page 45)
  - Foushee and Main Street Shelter (Oversize 45)
  - Franklin Residence, Boulevard and Main 1977 (Oversize 45)
  - Freas Residence (Oversize 45)
  - Freed, Robert L., Koger Executive Center, Henrico, Co. (Oversize 45)
  - Freeman, Friedman, Wilson and Carney Law Office (Oversize 45)
  - Galting Pointe Sales Office, Sales Office, isle of Wight (Oversize 46)
  - Gaspar, Dr. and Mrs. Patrick Residence, Lot 2 Boscobel, Goochland (Oversize 46)
  - Gates, Mr. and Mrs. Pearly, 11701 Young Manor Road (Oversize 46)
  - Gerencser, Mr. and Mrs. James, n.d. (Oversize 46)
  - Ghent Square, Westover, Norfolk, Va 1977 (Oversize 46)
  - Gibson, George D. 9 River Road [two sets] (Oversize 46)
  - Giles, Mr. and Mrs. Marvin, 104 Tempsford [two sets] (Oversize 46)
  - Godwin, William H., 6701 River Rd. (Oversize 46)
  - Goldman Residence, 7539 Riverside Drive (Oversize 46)
  - Goode, W.B. Offices, 416 West Franklin Street [three sets] (Oversize 46)
  - Goodwin Residence, 6701 River Road, (See Also 8625) (Oversize 46)
  - Goodwin Residence, Hanover Co. (Oversize 46)
  - Gordon, Mr. and Mrs. Page 1976 (Oversize 46)
  - Gottwald, Thomas E., 4503 Sulgrave Rd. 1992 (Oversize 46)
  - Gootwald, John D., Lower Tuckahoe, Goochland Co. 1990 (Oversize 46)
  - Graffiti, G.D. Restaurant 1921 (Oversize 46)
  - Grainer Residence 2006 Grove Avenue (Oversize 46)
  - Grigg Enterprises, Restaurant, 938 West or East Grace St. [two sets] (Oversize 46)
  - Grove Avenue Boundry Survey (Oversize 46)
  - Gundlach, H.C., Lot 16, Paxton (Oversize 46)
  - Gunter Resiedcence, 4704 Rolfe Avenue 1991 (Oversize 46)
  - Gutierrea, Fabio 112 Tempsford Lane (Oversize 46)
  - Hammonasset Beach Pavilion (Oversize 47)
  - Hancock, John B. III Residence, 5 Lorraine Station Road [two sets] (Oversize 47)
  - Hancock-Wirt Caskie House, WPA Drawings 1936 (Oversize 47)
  - Hancock Residence 1989 (Oversize 47)
  - Hancock Residence (Oversize 47)
  - Hardy, Robert Residence, Henrico Co. (Oversize 47)
  - Hargrove House, 2300 East Grace Street (Oversize 47)
  - Harland, Conrad P. (Oversize 47)
  - Harris, Mr. and Mrs. W. Gibson, Lockgreen Circle 1986 (Oversize 47)
  - Haskell, Howze 14 Bridgeway Road (Oversize 47)
  - Haskell, Richard B. Family Residence (Oversize 47)
  - Haverkampf, Mr. and Mrs. John, 8043 Riverside Drive 1991 (Oversize 47)
  - H.C. Yu and Associates, Health Center Office Addition for Henrico County office building, 709 East Grace Steet, J. Albert Heisler, architect 1956 (Oversize 47)
  - Henss, Mr. and Mrs. Werner, Addition to 2212 East Grace Street (Oversize 47)
  - Hermitage Country Club (Oversize 47)
  - Heritage Building, Main Street Association (Oversize 47)
  - Hickey Residence (Oversize 47)
  - Higgins, Mary D. and Kenneth R., property in Tuckahoe district, Henrico 1986 (Oversize 47)
  - Highland Park School (Copies of plans by architect Charles M. Robinson) (Oversize 47)
  - Highland Park United Methodist CHurch, 3001 Second Avenue 1990 (Oversize 47)
  - Hill, Robin B. fireplace (Oversize 47)
  - Hine, R. Spencer Residence, 5900 Three Chopt Road (Oversize 47)
  - Historic Petersburg Foundation Headquarters, 420 Grove Ave., Petersburg 1990 (Oversize 47)
  - Hollins College, President's House (Oversize 47)
  - Hollywood Cemetery, Caretaker's House 1989 (Oversize 47)
  - Hollywood Gate Cemetery, Gate House (Oversize 47)
  - Hollywood Cemetery, Superintendent House (Oversize 47)
  - Holt-Massey Residence [two sets] (Oversize 47)
  - Holt Residence [two sets] (Oversize 47)
  - Holt Residence, 5301 Toddsbury Rd. (Oversize 47)
  - Horwitz Residence, 118 Charnwood Rd. 1976 (Oversize 47)
  - Houghtaling, C.A., 213 Wexleigh (West Leigh?) Lane (Oversize 47)
  - Hudson Residence, 1911 Hanover Avenue (Oversize 47)
  - Hughes, A.F., 403 Old Locke Lane (Oversize 47)
  - Hull Residence, 2815 East Grace Street 1975 (Oversize 47)
  - Hunton Residence (Oversize 47)
  - Huntsinger, Mr. and Mrs. J. Residence (Oversize 47)
  - Income and Expenditures 1989 (Oversize 48)
  - Isemans, Sam Residence (Oversize 48)
  - Izenour Residence (Oversize 48)
  - Jade Elephant and Ludwigs, restaurants, 900 block of West Grace Street, Richmond, Va (Oversize 48)
  - James River Front (Oversize 48)
  - James River Front, Downtown (Oversize 48)
  - James River Front Elevations, Maps, and Ariel Views (Oversize 48)
  - James River Golf Course (Oversize 48)
  - Jefferson, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas Residence, 1429 Park Avenue (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Center 1979 (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish COmmunity Center, Athletic Facilities (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Center, Goochland County, Va (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Center, Preschool Facilities 1980 (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Center, Preschool Facilities 1980 (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Federation, 5403 Monument Avenue (Oversize 48)
  - Jewish Community Center, Succah (Oversize 48)
  - Johnston, W.T. residence, Lower Tuckahoe, Goochland County (Oversize 48)
  - Jonathan Edward College Library (Oversize 48)
  - Jones, O.H. 103 Culpepper Rd. (Oversize 48)
  - Jordan Residence, 10700 Greenmont Rd. (Oversize 48)
  - Kelly's, PB., 12-18 N. 17th Street (Oversize 49)
  - Kent-Valentine House, Garden Club of Virginia (Oversize 49)
  - Kent-Valentine House, Proposed Alterations to Carriage House (Oversize 49)
  - Kephart, Kip Caryhill, Charles City, Co. (Oversize 49)
  - Kilmers Point Urbanna, Va-Map of Lot Sites (Oversize 49)
  - Kirchdorfer, H. Norbert Residence, Cedar Strohme (Oversize 49)
  - King, Mr. and Mrs. T., 200 East Brook Run Drive (Oversize 49)
  - Kittrell, Dr. John Offices (Oversize 49)
  - Kjellstrom Residence [two sets, see also 7006] (Oversize 49)
  - Layfield, Mr. and Mrs. paul, Belmont New Kent County (Oversize 50)
  - Leeland Residence, Arlington Blvd, Charlottesville (Oversize 50)
  - Levin, Office for Dr. Jeffrey, D.D.S (Oversize 50)
  - Lewis, R.T. 3111-3113 W. Franklin Street (Oversize 50)
  - Library Pediment [unknown location] (Oversize 50)
  - Lindemann, Mr. and Mrs. Bohn Residence, 4206 Sulgrave Avenue [two sets] (Oversize 50)
  - Linden Row, Carriage House (Oversize 50)
  - Little Sister of the Poor (Oversize 50)
  - Lockgreen, Plan of [location unknown] (Oversize 50)
  - Lower Tuckahoe, Goochland Co. (Oversize 50)
  - Luck, Charles S. III, Winsack House, Goochland Co. 1986 (Oversize 50)
  - Luck Stone Corporation [several sets of plans with same name] (Oversize 50)
  - Luck Stone Corporation Alterations (Oversize 50)
  - Luck Stone Corporation Headquarters (Oversize 50)
  - Luck Stone Powhatan County Offices (Oversize 50)
  - Mansmann Reidence, Wayne, Pa (Oversize 51)
  - Masonic Temple Photographs (Oversize 51)
  - Matteer, E.G., 303 College Avenue
  - Maymont, Sliding Door for Carriage Shed (Oversize 51)
  - Maymont Wiring System (Oversize 51)
  - McCullough Residence, 403 N. Addison (Oversize 51)
  - McKeon, Mr. and Mrs. Jack, Old Gun Rd. (Oversize 51)
  - McElroy, Randie Residence, 110 N. Harvie Street (Oversize 51)
  - McHewse? Residence (Oversize 51)
  - McIver Residence at Windmill Point (Oversize 51)
  - Meiller, Dr. Joan, Chesterfield (Oversize 51)
  - Mercer, Mr. and Mrs. George, Jr. (Oversize 51)
  - Merdinger, Tortilla Flats (Oversize 51)
  - Meyers Residence, 215 El Dorado Drive (Oversize 51)
  - Mickell Residence, 3458 Northview Place (Oversize 51)
  - Midkiff Residence Revisions, 10 Cherokee Rd. 1991 (Oversize 51)
  - Miller, Stella and hugh, 2629 Grace Street (Oversize 51)
  - Moore, Hullie Residence (Oversize 51)
  - Morgan Residence, 504 Honaker Avenue (Oversize 51)
  - Mullen Residence, Brookwood Road (Oversize 51)
  - Mullen Residence, 2236 Brookwood Rd. (Oversize 51)
  - Murphy, Brian, 117 S. Wilton with 1937 drawing for Mr. and Mrs. Fred Todman at the same address (Oversize 51)
  - Museum of the Confederacy (Oversize 51)
  - Museum of the Confederacy 1988 (Oversize 51)
  - New Physicians Office, Petersburg, 615-617 S. Sycamore Street (Oversize 53)
  - New Temple Facility for Congregation AMI Huguenot Road (Oversize 53)
  - Newell Residence, Guest House (Oversize 53)
  - Newton, Mr. and Mrs. Carlton, 500 N. 25th St. 1985 (Oversize 53)
  - Nick's Restaurant, 8th and Main (Oversize 53)
  - Nicoll Residence, 3901 Dover Road (Oversize 53)
  - Nicoll, Mr. and Mrs. William, Jr. (Oversize 53)
  - Norman and Freed, 1010 N. Thompson Street (Oversize 53)
  - Norman, Sanford B., Dorset Woods South (Oversize 53)
  - Nunnally Residence (Oversize 53)
  - O. Van Sessoms, Additions and Alterations (Oversize 53)
  - Offices for Nikas, Englisby, and Barnes (Oversize 53)
  - Offices for Obenshaw, Hinnart, Ellyson, Rankel, and Bryant (Oversize 53)
  - Onacock, Virginia, Designs for Re-development 1974 (Oversize 53)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council, 816/818 Spring St. 1992 (Oversize 53)
  - Osdene Residence, 1806 Hanover Avenue (Oversize 53)
  - O'Tooles, Seating Plan 1978 (Oversize 53)
  - Oxford Church, Oxford, Maryland (Oversize 53)
  - Pace-King House Renovation (Oversize 54)
  - Pace-King House Renovation 1975 (Oversize 54)
  - Pace-King, Scope Services (Oversize 54)
  - Parker Beach House 8802 Ocean Front (Ave?), Virginia Beach (Oversize 54)
  - Parham Road Building Associates, 1703 Parham Rd. 1985 (Oversize 54)
  - Parrish, Mr. and Mrs. Jack Residence, 5324 Cary Street [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Parsley's Mill Subdivision Plan [drawer # 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Perel, Mr. and Mrs. Jonathan, Pool and Arbor at Ballyshannon, 500 Old Locke Lane [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Perrins, Mr. and Mrs. T., 1714 Park Avenue [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Peskin, Mary, 1209 East Cary Street (Oversize 54)
  - Pet East Franklin Association, 2001 East Franklin St. [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Pet East Franklin Association, 2001 East Franklin St. 1983 (Oversize 54)
  - Pierce, B.B. House Lot [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Pierce Trailer Service, North Carolina [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Plans/Elevations for Unknown House (Oversize 54)
  - Plans for an Unknown Site (Oversize 54)
  - Plans for an Unkown Staircase, Osdene Residence (Oversize 54)
  - Plans for Unknown Residence (Oversize 54)
  - Plans for Unknown Site (Oversize 54)
  - Plans for Unkown Site (Oversize 54)
  - Pleasant Hill Reception Center Plans [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Poe Shrine, Bath and Kitchen Plans (Oversize 54)
  - Powers, Frank Residence, (Todd Residence?) [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Prestwould, Alterations to residence 1985 (Oversize 54)
  - Proposed Offices for OBensham, Hinnant, Ellyson, Rankle, and Bryant (Oversize 54)
  - Proposed Wiring System for Maymont 1926 (Oversize 54)
  - Providence Hall Plans, Williamsburg [drawer 65] (Oversize 54)
  - Providence Hall, Williamsburg (Oversize 54)
  - Providence Hall, Williamsburg (Oversize 54)
  - Ranjit Sen, 1138 West Avenue (Oversize 54)
  - Renovation of 43 East Williamsburg Road (Oversize 54)
  - Residence at Lot 22 (Oversize 54)
  - Residence at Lot 36 (Oversize 54)
  - Residence at Robin Hill 1990 (Oversize 54)
  - Richardson Residence, 1501 North 35th Street (Oversize 54)
  - Rich-Mar Corporation Offices, 1703 Parham Road (Oversize 54)
  - Richmond, 2.7 Acres fo City Blocks (Oversize 54)
  - Richmond Jewish Community Center (Oversize 54)
  - Richmond Jewish Community Center, The Succah (Oversize 54)
  - Richmond Landmarks Drawing (Oversize 54)
  - Richmond Redevelopment Housing Authority, Public Housing [3 sets] RRHA Public Housing 7-24 1982 (Oversize 54)
  - Reiland, Robert, 930 Mooreland Rd 1984 (Oversize 54)
  - Riley, Mrs. Anne, 3449 W. Cary St. 1992 (Oversize 54)
  - Riley, Mrs. Anne, Alterations to 3449 West Cary Street (Oversize 54)
  - Robertson, Mr. and Mrs. Harry W., III Residence (Oversize 54)